<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Privacy Indicators</string>
    <string name="service_description">When this service is enabled it lets \'Privacy Indicators App\' to display notifications and indicators
        every time a third-party app or a service uses camera or microphone on any screen.
        \n\nThis Service/App doesn\'t have any permission to use internet or your device\'s camera, microphone or any other Hardware. And will NOT gather any data whatsoever.
    </string>
    <string name="service_summary">Get notified every time a third-party app uses camera or microphone</string>
    <string name="made_by">Made with ❤ by Nitish</string>
    <string name="built_by">Built in FOSS HACKS 2020</string>

    <string name="notification_alert_summary">You will get an active notification on the status bar while an app is using your camera or microphone.</string>

    <string name="indicators_disabled_description">Click on the above Switch and Turn on the Privacy Indicator in the Accessibility Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy_indicators_disabled_title">Privacy Indicators are disabled</string>

    <string name="camera_indicator_title">Camera Indicator</string>
    <string name="camera_indicator_description">This feature toggle will enable Camera Indicator which will notify you every time when a third-party app or service tried to access your Camera Hardware.</string>

    <string name="microphone_indicator_title">Microphone Indicator</string>
    <string name="microphone_indicator_description">This feature toggle will enable Microphone Indicator which will notify you every time when a third-party app or service tried to access your Microphone.</string>

    <string name="location_indicator_title">Location Indicator</string>
    <string name="location_indicator_description">GPS Hardware usage indicator.  This feature is still under development. Will be functional from next release.</string>

    <string name="vibration_alert_title">Vibration Alert</string>
    <string name="vibration_alert_description">Turning this on will give you a haptic feedback to indicate camera and microphone usage of any third-party app or service.</string>

    <string name="notification_alert_title">Notification Alert</string>
    <string name="notification_alert_description">Turning this on will give you a foreground notification when ever the camera or microphone usage is detected.</string>

    <string name="customization_center_title">Customize Indicators</string>
    <string name="customization_center_description">You can customise how, where and which indicators to be appeared. Configure the look and feel of Indicators</string>

    <string name="indicator_logs_title">Indicator Logs</string>
    <string name="indicator_logs_description">View the summary of Camera, Microphone and Location usage by various apps. Arranged in chronological order and statistically displayed. (Inspired from Android 12)</string>

    <string name="share_title">Share with your friends</string>
    <string name="share_description">Spread the power of privacy control to your friends and also rate us on Play store if you feel this app useful.</string>

    <string name="report_issue_title">Report Issue or Request Feature</string>
    <string name="report_issue_description">This app is completely open-source. If you have any issue or willing to request a feature click here to go to GitHub repo.</string>
</resources>
